Finding Aid for the Philippine Comics Collection LSC.2386
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Ella Arcangel, 2016-2017
  - Lupang mga Naglaho, 2017; 1 item
- Ang Morion, 2015-2017
  This is a comic book series inspired by a local festival in the town of Marinduque called Moriones, celebrated every Holy Week. It is based on the premise that God made three creatures at the beginning of time: angels, humans, and djinn.
  Creator: Wan Malinao Mañanita
  - Ang Morion vol.2 issue 1, 2015; 1 item
  - Ang Morion vol.2 issue 2, 2017; 1 item
- Anarchy Inc. #1 and #2, 2 items
  This is a comic series about anarchists who use their superpowers to protect the streets from syndicate families fighting for territorial control. Although the anarchists work individually and fight each other over territories they patrol, a mysterious anarchist comes onto the scene and proposes that they all work together.
  Creator: Chuck Llanto
  Publisher: Eventual Empire
- Muros: The Cemetery Girl, Parts 1, 2, and 3, 2015-2017; 3 items
  A three-part comic book series about a dystopian Manila, a place that has turned into one of sin and danger.
  Creators: Paolo Chikiamco; Borg Sinaban
- Crime-fighting Call Center Agents, 2011-2013
  This is a comic book series about a group of call center agents who frequently run into supernatural beings and situations that call for them to fight.
  Creators: Noel Pascual; AJ Bernardo
  Publisher: Kowtow Komiks
  - Crime-fighting Call Center Agents #1: Psycho Killer On A Bike, 2011; 1 item
  - Crime-fighting Call Center Agents #2: Pag-uulayaw Sa Barrio Namayapa part 1 of 2, 2012; 1 item
  - Crime-fighting Call Center Agents #3: Pag-uulayaw Sa Barrio Namayapa part 2 of 2, 2012; 1 item
  - Crime-fighting Call Center Agents #4, 2013; 1 item
- Kayaw
  Kayaw is a three-part comic series that follows the story of a female Japanese intelligence officer named Kamiko as she embarks on her mission to conquer the Kalinga mountains in the Philippines. Despite the sheer force and advanced war technology of the Imperial Japanese Army, they are no match for the indigenous headhunters who know the terrain of Kalinga like no other. The comics advertise Katribu Tatu, a subgroup of the Katribu Art Movement, who specialize in giving customized indigenous tattoos that are similar to the ones seen on the Kalinga warriors in the comics.
  Creators: Steve Magay; Dax
  Publisher: Hollowpoint Studios
  - Kayaw (part 1 of 3), 2014 April; 1 item
  - Kayaw (part 2 of 3), 2016 April; 1 item
- Ignition Comix Issues 1 and 2, 2 items
  Ignition Comix is a compilation of four different stories published by Atomic Monkey Production in Makati City, Philippines.
  Creators: Michael Del Mundo; Michael Seludo